{
  "decks": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "name": "111ssRe2ndering in React EDITSssdas",
      "description": "Reacts component structure allowsass for quickly building a complex web application that relies on DOM manipulation. "
    },
    {
      "name": "React Router",
      "description": "React Router is a collection of navigational components that compose declaratively with your application.",
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "name": "DN",
      "description": "DD",
      "id": 3
    }
  ],
  "cards": [
    {
      "id": 2,
      "front": "TTTTTTTFRESHHow do you modify the state of a different React component?",
      "back": "Not at all! State isss visible to the component only.",
      "deckId": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "front": "111How do you pass data 'down' to a React dchild component?",
      "back": "As properties or propssss",
      "deckId": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "What path will match the follow Route?\n<Route>\n  <NotFound />\n</Route>",
      "back": "All paths. A route with no path matches all URL's",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "front": "What does <Switch> do?",
      "back": "Renders the first matching child <Route> ",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "front": [
        "asd"
      ],
      "back": [
        "asd"
      ],
      "deckId": null,
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "front": [
        "asdasd"
      ],
      "back": [
        "asdasd"
      ],
      "deckId": null,
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "front": [
        "asdsa"
      ],
      "back": [
        "asdsa"
      ],
      "deckId": null,
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "front": [
        "asdsa"
      ],
      "back": [
        "asdsa"
      ],
      "deckId": null,
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "front": [
        "asdsaf"
      ],
      "back": [
        "asdsaf"
      ],
      "deckId": null,
      "id": 10
    },
    {
      "front": [
        "asd"
      ],
      "back": [
        "asv"
      ],
      "deckId": null,
      "id": 11
    },
    {
      "front": [
        "asda"
      ],
      "back": [
        "asda"
      ],
      "deckId": null,
      "id": 12
    },
    {
      "front": [
        "asd"
      ],
      "back": [
        "asd"
      ],
      "deckId": null,
      "id": 13
    },
    {
      "front": [
        "asd"
      ],
      "back": [
        "asd"
      ],
      "deckId": null,
      "id": 14
    },
    {
      "front": [
        "asd"
      ],
      "back": [
        "asd"
      ],
      "deckId": null,
      "id": 15
    },
    {
      "front": "Jjjjj",
      "back": "Jjjjj",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 22
    },
    {
      "front": "1cad s33",
      "back": "1cad s33ss",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 23
    },
    {
      "front": "2card f",
      "back": "2card bbbb",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 24
    },
    {
      "front": "xzxx",
      "back": "xzxz",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 25
    },
    {
      "front": "dfdfd",
      "back": "dfdfdf",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 26
    },
    {
      "front": "AddF",
      "back": "AddB",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 27
    },
    {
      "front": "AddE",
      "back": "AddR",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 28
    },
    {
      "front": "Add3",
      "back": "Add4",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 29
    },
    {
      "front": "RRR",
      "back": "RRR",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 30
    },
    {
      "front": "DFF",
      "back": "DFV",
      "deckId": 3,
      "id": 32
    },
    {
      "front": "DVC",
      "back": "DCC",
      "deckId": 3,
      "id": 33
    },
    {
      "front": "ADA",
      "back": "ADD",
      "deckId": 3,
      "id": 34
    }
  ]
}